A Guide to the David Rockefeller Personal and Professional papers, RG 1 and RG 2 FA436
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller, 1918-1981; 1945-1961; 2; 19.37 Cubic Feet 51 letter document boxes
  - Cultural
    - American Philosophical Society, 1959-1973 (Box 7, Folder 98)
      DR a member. Not active.
    - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      DR a trustee. Resignation. Served on committee on terrestrial science. Elihu Root Jr. and Vannevar Bush correspondence.
    - Colonial Williamsburg, 1927, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      Reproduced images of two handwritten letters from DR to Rev. Dr. W.A.R. Goodwin of Colonial Williamsburg.
    - Great Books of the Western World, 1949-1952 (Box 8, Folder 101)
      DR purchase of book sets. Financial difficulties of project.
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1946-1952 (Box 8, Folder 102)
      DR contributions. Board member. Museum activities and planning. Tributes to AAR. Gifts of art. Advice to him on purchases of art. Permission to reproduce pieces he owns. Correspondence with Blanchette Rockefeller.
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1953-1958 (Box 8, Folder 103)
      DR contributions. Board member. Museum activities and planning. Tributes to AAR. Gifts of art. Advice to him on purchases of art. Permission to reproduce pieces he owns. Correspondence with Blanchette Rockefeller. Planning of thirtieth anniversary of the museum.
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Museum of Modern Art, thirtieth anniversary, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 107)
      Planning of thirtieth anniversary of the museum.
    - Museum of Modern Art, auction of paintings, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - New York Philharmonic Society, 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 109)
      Mrs. DR and Richard Dana served on development committee.
    - Rhode Island School of Design, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 110)
      Three exhibit rooms designed in memory of AAR. Correspondence with Philip Johnson, designing architect of the rooms.
  - Education
    - Chapin School, 1953-1960 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      100 East End Avenue, New York. Private girls high school. DR's four daughters attended. DR on board of trustees; functions while on board. Fundraising--Chapin School Guarantee Fund. Comments on prospective trustees and students. Contributions. Independent School Fund of NYC. DR's resignation from board.
    - Harvard University, general, 1946-1950 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      DR contributions to such things as graduate center, Rogg Museum, Harvard Foundation for Advanced Study and Research, William Waite Waters Scholarship Fund. DR's many interests in Harvard (e.g., alumni association, Harvard Fund Council, Harvard Crimson, Arnold Arboretum controversy. Reunions.
    - Harvard University, general, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Harvard University, general, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Harvard University, general, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Harvard University, general, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Harvard University, general, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Harvard University, athletics department, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 118)
      Various problems connected with athletic program at Harvard and the Ivy League: large expenditures of money, methodsof recruiting athletes, "brains vs. brawn." DR on comittee to visit the departmennt of athletics.
    - Harvard University, athletics department, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Harvard University, economics department committee, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 120)
      DR serving as Vice Chair on the Overseers Committee to Visit the Department of Economics; appointments to the committee. Appointments to the faculty in the economics department, DR comments. DR comments on lack of balance in the economics department. DR's general criticism and comments on the department; teaching problems; closer relationship between businessmen and economists.
    - Harvard University, economics department committee, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Harvard University, economics department committee, 1951-1960 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Harvard University, Lamont Library, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 123)
      DR contributions. DR plaque in memory of classmates killed in World War II. Lamont Library endowment solicitation.
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1947-1955 (Box 10, Folder 124)
      The proper position of the museum in the University and in the Boston area. Work done by the museum. Fund raising. Committee to Visit the Museum.
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1956 January-February (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1956 March-April (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1956 May-December (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1958 January-July (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1958 October-December (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1959 January-March (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1959 April-December (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Harvard University, Board of Overseers, 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 134)
      DR very active on the Board. Meetings. Nomination and election of people to the Board. DR an Associate of Leverett House.
    - Harvard University, Board of Overseers, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Harvard University, Board of Overseers, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Harvard University, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Professorship of Oriental Art, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 137)
      DR's idea to establish this professorship. Contributions for it. Reactions to establishing it. Professor Max Loehr as first recipient of AAR professorship.
    - Harvard University, "A Program for Harvard College", 1956-1957 May (Box 12, Folder 138)
      Fundraising program with goal of $82 million for Harvard College. Solicitations by DR and others. Various contributors; refusals; fundraising dinners, speeches (DR). DR contributions--largest contributor. NAR and JDR 3rd contributions.
    - Harvard University, "A Program for Harvard College", 1957 June-1958 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - Harvard University, "A Program for Harvard College", 1959 January-May (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Harvard University, "A Program for Harvard College", 1959 June-1961 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Harvard University, class of 1936 twenty-fifth reunion, 1959-1961 March (Box 12, Folder 142)
      Preparation for 25th class reunion, DR class of 1936. DR elected Chief Marshal for 1961 reunion; duties.
    - Harvard University, class of 1936 twenty-fifth reunion, 1961 April-August (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Harvard University, class of 1936 twenty-fifth reunion art exhibit, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 144)
      DR lent paintings.
    - Harvard University, Harvard and MIT visiting committee on Joint Center for Urban Studies, 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 145)
      Committee's inception. Invitation to DR to become a member. Problems of dealing with urban renewal.
    - Harvard University, visiting committee, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 146)
      DR Chair. Reports and comments by various members of the committee on 1) visit to the Museum of Comparative Zoology, 2) vist to Radcliffe, 3) suggested raise in student tuition, 4) visit to athletic department, 5) new residence house at Harvard. Selection of committee members. Meetings. Literature pertinent to various subjects.
    - Harvard University, visiting committee, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 147)
    - Harvard University, visiting committee, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - Harvard University, visiting committee, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Harvard University, visiting committee, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Harvard University, visiting committee, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Milton Academy, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 152)
      Girls school in Milton, Massachusetts. Milton Academy advancement program. Contributions by DR.
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1955-1960 (Box 14, Folder 153)
      Prep school in Exeter, New Hampshire. David Rockefeller Jr. attended. DR contributions.
    - Pocantico Hills School, 1952-1959 (Box 14, Folder 155)
      Contributions by DR. Consolidated school movement. Citizens advisory committee.
    - University of Chicago, 1949-1954 (Box 14, Folder 156)
      DR trustee. Listings of the members of the Board of Trustees. DR's function as a trustee; comments on prospective trustees; policy decisions; dinners; speeches; fundraising. DR contributions. Rockefeller Memorial Chapel. Institute of International Studies.
    - University of Chicago, 1955-1960 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Employees, 1941-1956 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    Restricted from access - personnel material.
  - Finances
    - General correspondence, 1918-1940 (Box 14, Folder 159)
      Investments; gifts; savings.
    - General correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - General correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 14, Folder 160a)
    - General correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - Allowance, 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Childhood savings, 1920-1934 (Box 14, Folder 163)
      JDR will match all voluntary savings.
    - Chase Bank business account, 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Chase Bank household account, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Chase Bank personal account, 1932-1941 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Chase Bank salary and promotions, 1948-1959 (Box 14, Folder 168)
    - Chase Bank salary and promotions, 1948-1959 (Box 14, Folder 168a)
    - East River Savings Bank account, 1938-1940 (Box 15, Folder 169)
    - Emmigrant Indiana Savings Bank account, 1935-1940 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Gifts, 1934-1949 (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Gifts, 1934-1949 (Box 15, Folder 171a)
      Restricted from access. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from access.
    - Securities, 1931-1946 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Securities, 1931-1946 (Box 15, Folder 172a)
    - Securities, 1947-1961 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    - Securities, 1947-1961 (Box 15, Folder 173a)
  - Foreign affairs
    - American-Korean Foundation, 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 174)
      DR a director of foundation. Contributions to Korean relief following war. Changes in policy.
    - British Outlook, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 175)
      DR interest in publication to explain England to the United States; did not materialize.
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, general, 1948-1955 (Box 15, Folder 176)
      DR a trustee. Service on committees. Resignation. Programs and projects. Contributions. Alger Hiss hearings and correspondence--one piece of signed original from Hiss.
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, general, 1956-1961 (Box 15, Folder 177)
      DR a trustee. Service on committees. Resignation. Programs and projects. Contributions.
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, new building, 1949-1955 (Box 15, Folder 178)
      DR a trustee. Service on committees. Planning and construction of buildings on United Nations plaza.
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Cox Committee investigation, 1952-1954 (Box 16, Folder 179)
      DR a trustee. Service on committees. U.S. Congress's Cox Committee investigation.
    - Committee for Foreign Service Center, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 180)
      Formation of Washington Foreign Service Center as meeting place for educational and social purposes. DR member of committee.
    - Comittee for a National Trade Policy, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 181)
      DR contributions.
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1946-1954 (Box 16, Folder 182)
      DR a member and officer. Council activities and fundraising. DR served on membership committee. Richard Gilder memorial fund.
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1955-1961 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - "Education for International Understanding," article by Milton Eisenhower, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - Richard Gilder memorial, 1946-1948 (Box 16, Folder 185)
      Creation and fundraising for Council on Foreign Relations memorial library fund for Richard Gilder.
    - Government Affairs Foundation, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 186)
      DR contributions for foundation created by brother Nelson. NAR's letter on purpose of the foundation.
    - United Nations investment committee, 1952-1955 (Box 16, Folder 187)
      DR a member. Meeting of executive committee. Chase Bank investments. Fee paid to DR turned over to UN International Children's Emergency Fund.
    - United Nations official dinners, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 188)
      DR attended.
  - Fund for Frau Bermann, 1939-1942 (Box 16, Folder 189)
    DR and other former pupils of Frau Bermann sent her money in Germany during World War II.
  - Funds for Republican party, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 190)
    Memo on supporting party in midterm elections.
  - Homes
    - London house, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 191)
      DR rented home in London for the summer from Oliver I. Parker for the coronation of Queen Elizabeth II.
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, general, 1948-1952 (Box 16, Folder 192)
      DR's first home in Seal Harbor, "Westward Cottage," a gift from JDR Jr. Contributions to community activities. Purchase and sale of real estate. Beatrix Farrand correspondence.
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, general, 1953-1957 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, general, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 194)
      AAR garden at the Eyrie. Maintenance, employer-employee policies, retirement policies, property at the Eyrie after JDR Jr.'s death. DR gifts. Peabody Drive improvement. Adacia National Park, property left by JDR Jr. to the park. Northeast Harbor library scholarship committee. Seal Harbor yacht club. Northeast Harbor fleet. Mt. Desert Island regional schools.
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, Angell House ("Firwood"), 1953-1956 (Box 17, Folder 195)
      Also called "Firwood." DR purchased house. Repairs. Rented to Mr. and Mrs. W. Lord. Sale of house to Mr. and Mrs. Lord.
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, Donald Bryant, 1953-1960 (Box 17, Folder 196)
      Summer employee at Seal Harbor who took care of DR's boats. Salary increases. DR pleased with his work.
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, Donald Bryant, 1953-1960 (Box 17, Folder 196a)
    - Seal Harbor, Maine, Mt. Desert Development Corporation, 1953-1959 (Box 17, Folder 197)
      DR stockholder in Mt. Desert Development Corporation; puchase of stock. Research work on Mt. Desert Island. Attracting industry to the island. Problems of zoning.
    - New York, 1060 Fifth Avenue apartment, 1945-1947 (Box 17, Folder 198)
      Renting apartment. Work done inside apartment.
    - New York, East 65th Street house, purchase, 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 199)
      Purchase from Ernest Iselin
    - New York, East 65th Street house, purchase, 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 199a)
    - New York, East 65th Street house, general, 1948-1955 (Box 17, Folder 200)
      Purchase of items for house: furniture, dishes, silver, objets d'art; antiques from London, France, and U.S. Issues with street widening, fence. Correspondence with Mott B. Schmidt.
    - New York, East 65th Street house, general, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 201)
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, General, 1940-1949 (Box 17, Folder 202)
      DR home, Hudson Pines. Formerly known as Stevens House. Renovation, landscaping, purchase of furniture and objets d'art. Maintenance. Deer in Pocantico. Beatrix Farrand correspondence. Horses. Art collection and loans of works of arts.
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, General, 1940-1949 (Box 17, Folder 202a)
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, General, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 203)
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, General, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 204)
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, General, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 204a)
      Restricted from access - confidential material.
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, Swimming Center, 1957-1961 (Box 18, Folder 205)
      JDR Jr. contributes swimming pool center to school district. Planning and construction.
    - Pocantico Hills, New York, Tarrytown survey, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - Wyoming, JY Ranch, 1948-1961 (Box 18, Folder 207)
      Jackson Hole Preserve, Rockefeller ranch. Visits by members of the whole family during the summer. Red Mathews and his wife, Belle, run the ranch.
    - Wyoming, JY Ranch, 1948-1961 (Box 18, Folder 207a)
  - Invitations: Weddings, 1940; n.d. (Box 18, Folder 208)
    DR and MMR's wedding; MMR's parents' wedding (Francis Sims McGrath and Neva Van Zandt Smith)
  - Invitations: General, 1946-1961 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    Invitations to luncheons, dinners, art exhibits. Invitation for DR to speak at various functions, mostly declined. Dinner given by DR.
  - Paintings
    Purchasing, lending, cataloguing of DR's works of art.
    - 1945-1954 (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 212)
    - 1959 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    - 1959 (Box 18, Folder 213a)
    - 1960 (Box 18, Folder 214)
    - 1961 January-June (Box 19, Folder 215)
    - 1961 July-1962 (Box 19, Folder 216)
    - Edward G. Robinson collection, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 217)
      DR and LSR bid unsuccessfully on paintings in the collection of actor Edward G. Robinson.
  - Pocantico Hills Union Church, 1946, 1952-1959 (Box 19, Folder 218)
    Planning committee chair and resignation; proposed building plans; children's wing and Sunday school addition; pledges and gifts to church; DR as Santa Claus; DR talk at men's club meeting; church budget; AAR memorial rose window by Matisse booklet.
  - Protestant Council, 1947-1956 (Box 19, Folder 219)
    DR a director. His ideas on programs and policies.
  - Rockefeller boards
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 219.1)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1951-1955 (Box 19, Folder 220)
      Individuals asking for financial assistance. Cox resolution on Senate Investigation of Foundations. Internal response by RF.
    - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (Rockefeller University), 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 221)
      DR a trustee, chair of the board. Institute concerts. Faculty and Staff Club, Inc. DR contributions. Brief history fo the Institute. AAR Hall. Commencement exercises. Brimble's article. Development committee--future planning, creation of committee, people to serve. Detlev Bronk correspondence.
    - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (Rockefeller University), 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 221a)
    - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research: Medical Center Neighborhood Association, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 222)
      Proposed creation of association. Barklie M. Henry's ideas. Comments by DR as member of Institute board.
    - York Avenue Redevelopment Project, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 223)
      Plan to provide for Memorial Hospital and Rockefeller Institute middle-income staff housing. Purchase of property. Institute's decision to pull out of plan and sell land to Memorial.
    - York Avenue Redevelopment Project, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Trips
    - General, 1934-1952 (Box 19, Folder 225)
      Some of DR's handwritten expense tallies for reimbursement by Chase Bank. DR's handwritten notes on people he met with during trips. 1951 purchases in Europe.
    - General, 1934-1952 (Box 19, Folder 225a)
    - General, 1953-1961 (Box 19, Folder 226)
      1953 Europe and the Middle East. 1954 South America. 1956 Europe. 1959 Africa. Includes receipts of fine arts purchases.
    - General, 1953-1961 (Box 19, Folder 226a)
    - England cylcing tour in Summer 1932, 1932-1933 (Box 20, Folder 227)
    - England cylcing tour in Summer 1932, 1932-1933 (Box 20, Folder 227a)
    - Munich, Germany in Summer 1933, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 228)
    - Germany and Poland in Summer 1935, 1935-1936 (Box 20, Folder 229)
      Trip to Germany, France, and possibly Eastern Europe
    - Germany, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 230)
    - London, England (year at London School of Economics), 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 231)
    - London, England (year at London School of Economics), 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 231a)
    - Passport numbers, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 232)
    - Cuba, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 233)
      Mostly clippings from Cuban press. Includes translations.
  - Wedding
    - Wedding to Margaret (Peggy) McGrath, 1940 September 7 (Box 20, Folder 234)
      DR marries Margaret McGrath in Bedford, New York. Lists of guests. Correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. McGrath. Well-wishes. Newspaper clippings. Trip to Seal Harbor.
    - Gifts, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 235)
      JDR Jr. and others' wedding gifts.
    - Gifts, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 235a)
      Restricted from access - financial material.
    - Honeymoon: Trip to JY Ranch, Wyoming, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 236)
  - Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller
    - General, 1941-1961 (Box 20, Folder 237)
      Correspondence with JDR Jr. Civilian Defense volunteer worker during WWII. Contributions. U.S. wildflower publication project. Requests to participate in benefit events. Household purchases.
    - General, 1941-1961 (Box 20, Folder 237a)
    - Gifts, 1940-1959 (Box 20, Folder 238)
      From JDR Jr.
    - Gifts, 1940-1959 (Box 20, Folder 238a)
    - Finances, 1941-1958 (Box 20, Folder 239)
      Purchase of securities. Allowance for household. Checking account.
    - Finances, 1941-1958 (Box 20, Folder 239a)
    - Trust Fund notices, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 240)
      Nonsensitive matters concerning trust.
    - Bankers Trust Company account, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Chase Bank accounts, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - Personal correspondence, 1939-1961
    Alphabetical arrangement of correspondence received into and sent out from Family Office at Room 5600 of 30 Rockefeller Plaza, New York.
    - Ab-Am, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 257)
    - Ab-Am, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 257a)
    - An-Au, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 258)
    - Bac-Barnes, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 259)
    - Barr-Bazin, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - Bea-Bel, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 261)
    - Bem-Ben, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - Ber-Bey, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - Bi-Bl, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - Boa-Boy, 1939-1961 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - Bra-Bry, 1939-1961 (Box 23, Folder 266)
    - Buc-But, 1939-1961 (Box 23, Folder 267)
    - Cac-Car, 1939-1961 (Box 23, Folder 268)
    - Cas-Cha, 1939-1961 (Box 23, Folder 269)
    - Chavallier, 1939-1961 (Box 23, Folder 270)
    - Chevreux-Cliburn, 1939-1961 (Box 23, Folder 271)
    - Coc-Coo, 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 272)
    - Cor-Cut, 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 273)
    - Dac-Dav, 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 274)
    - Dac-Dav, 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 274a)
    - Deb-Deg, 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 275)
    - Del-Der, 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 276)
    - de Rosen, 1948-1950 (Box 24, Folder 277)
    - de Rosen, 1951-1961 (Box 24, Folder 278)
    - des-Dra, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 279)
    - des-Dra, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 279a)
    - Dro-Dul, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 280)
    - Dun-Dyk, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 281)
    - Dun-Dyk, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 281a)
    - Ea-Eh, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 282)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 283)
    - Ei-Eme, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 284)
    - Emm-Eys, 1939-1961 (Box 25, Folder 285)
    - Fab-Fay, 1939-1961 (Box 26, Folder 286)
    - Fab-Fay, 1939-1961 (Box 26, Folder 286a)
    - Fe-Fi, 1939-1961 (Box 26, Folder 287)